Daniel Mason

Frontend Developer
Full Stack Test Automation Engineer





Frontend Developer and a Full Stack Test Automation Engineer specializing in frontend development & Test Automation with Java. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Portfolio ready with over 50 Projects. Wellversed in numerous programming languages and platform including HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, React, Java and WordPress. Strong background in project management and customer relations.



PROFESSIONAL SKILL

HTML, CSS, Tailwind

JavaScript, React, Node.js

Java, Selenium, Appium

TestNG, Maven, Jenkins

REST API & Database (MySQL) Testing

Desktop & Electron Testing

Jira & GitHub

Data-Driven Testing

WordPress & Shopify Store Build

eBay, Amazon Shop Operations

Photoshop

Networking / TCP/IP

Linux & Network Security

Blockchain & Cryptocurrency



WORK EXPERIENCES

Freelancer / 2022

QBO Services / 2020 – 2021

Frontend Developer: Developed and structured feature-rich client websites with high quality code. Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive

interactions and experiences. Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability. Applied version control software (Git) to track,

Lavan Group / 2019 - 2020

Junior Frontend Developer: Cooperated with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences. Worked with senior developer to manage large, complex design project. Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites. Carried out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize

Business owner of a large-scale drop-shipping operation / 2013 - 2019

Managed large order volume. Took on automation challenges, extensive use of third-party ecommerce tools including building and managing Shopify stores. Effectively running & managing customer service. Experience with staff/VA management.

"RSA" Analyst – 2011

Detection and treatment of financial fraud. Provided technical support for bank customers cases such as "Fishing"



EDUCATION

FULL STACK AUTOMATION COURSE (Admitted via Ministry of Innovation Program) / 2021 - 2022

ATID College: Instructor - Yoni Flener

BACHELORS DEGREE / 2012

H.I.T | Holon Institute of Technology: Instructional Design.

BACHELORS DEGREE / 2009

QUT | Queensland University of Technology: Information Technology

PERSONAL SKILL

CREATIVE	TEAM WORK	
MANAGEMENT	INNOVATE	